printfile.com 2017-05-14

# Print File | Archival Supplies | Photo Storage Products - Privacy Policy

---  
|  | 

Home > Privacy Policy

| | |   
---|---|---  
| 

#### Privacy Policy

This online privacy statement specifies what information Print File collects online, as well as how it is used.

**What Personal Information is Collected?**  
In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. The information we learn from customers, however, helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at [www.PrintFile.com](http://www.printfile.com/).

**Information You Give Us:**  
Print File, Inc. receives and stores personal information about you when you subscribe to a service, register to receive brochures, or participate in contests, sweepstakes and/or promotions. This information may include your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, and email. You may choose not to provide such information.

Credit card data and registration information is protected by Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") or other encryption mechanisms. Online Payment Processing for [www.PrintFile.com](http://www.printfile.com/) is processed by PayPal Payflow Pro. Print File, Inc. does not store credit card information.

Print File, Inc. cautions visitors to its websites that no network, including the internet, is entirely secure. Accordingly, we cannot be responsible for loss, corruption or unauthorized acquisition of personal information provided to our websites, or for any damages resulting from such loss, corruption or unauthorized acquisition.

**How is Information Used?  
**__Emails__ \- If you provide the PrintFile.com web site with your e-mail address, you may receive e-mails from Print File.com web site.  
__"Contact Us" and Comments Features__ \- Print File, Inc encourages visitors to its websites to contact us with questions and/or comments. Email addresses and other information of persons using these features may be collected in order to facilitate our responses to those inquiries.  
__Catalog Mailing List__ \- If you provide your name and address, we will add you to our mailing list and we may send you catalogs as a result of visiting our website. If you prefer not to receive catalogs from us, please contact us at [support@printfile.com](mailto:support@printfile.com) or 800-508-8539 and ask to be taken off our mailing list.  
__Sharing with Other Companies__ \- Print File, Inc. does not sell or rent personal information about you to any third parties. We may however, share information with carefully selected Third Party Service Providers, vendors, business partners and other organizations who provide support services to us (such as printer, mailing house, web host, order fulfillment, shipping, customer service, data management and promotional services) or that help us market our products and services. We provide these companies with the information needed for them to perform their functions.

**Links to Third Party Sites:**  
The PrintFile.com website may include links to other web sites that are not under our control. These other web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting those websites.

Discount Codes and Gift Certificates do not apply to Blurb photo books.

**Policy Changes:**  
This policy is subject to change. If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our website.

*Note: Print File, Inc sells the same or similar products as www.lightimpressionsdirect.com but are not affiliated in any way with Light Impressions or New Century Direct.

Back to top

|   
| |   
|   
---  
  
Receive our latest   
news and offers by email.

---  
  
Click to explore our electronic catalog  
  
|  |  | 

[

](https://www.bbb.org/central-florida/business-reviews/photo-imaging-service/print-file-in-apopka-fl-90404884#sealclick "Click for the Business Review of Print File, Inc., a TBD in Apopka FL") |  [ ](http://www.printfile.com/satisfaction-guarantee.aspx) |   
---|---|---|---|---
